{
    "task_name": "named-entity-recognition",
    "system_name": null,
    "dataset_name": "dataset_name",
    "metric_names": [
        "f1_score_seqeval"
    ],
    "features": {
        "tokens": {
            "feature": {
                "dtype": "string",
                "description": null,
                "is_bucket": false,
                "is_pre_computed": false,
                "bucket_info": null,
                "_type": "Value"
            },
            "length": -1,
            "is_bucket": false,
            "_type": "Sequence"
        },
        "ner_true_tags": {
            "feature": {
                "num_classes": 9,
                "names": [
                    "O",
                    "B-PER",
                    "I-PER",
                    "B-ORG",
                    "I-ORG",
                    "B-LOC",
                    "I-LOC",
                    "B-MISC",
                    "I-MISC"
                ],
                "description": null,
                "names_file": null,
                "is_bucket": false,
                "is_pre_computed": false,
                "bucket_info": null,
                "_type": "ClassLabel"
            },
            "length": -1,
            "is_bucket": false,
            "_type": "Sequence"
        },
        "ner_pred_tags": {
            "feature": {
                "num_classes": 9,
                "names": [
                    "O",
                    "B-PER",
                    "I-PER",
                    "B-ORG",
                    "I-ORG",
                    "B-LOC",
                    "I-LOC",
                    "B-MISC",
                    "I-MISC"
                ],
                "description": null,
                "names_file": null,
                "is_bucket": false,
                "is_pre_computed": false,
                "bucket_info": null,
                "_type": "ClassLabel"
            },
            "length": -1,
            "is_bucket": false,
            "_type": "Sequence"
        },
        "sentence_length": {
            "dtype": "float32",
            "description": "sentence length",
            "is_bucket": true,
            "is_pre_computed": false,
            "bucket_info": {
                "_method": "bucket_attribute_specified_bucket_value",
                "_number": 4,
                "_setting": []
            },
            "_type": "Value"
        },
        "true_entity_info": {
            "feature": {
                "feature": {
                    "span_text": {
                        "dtype": "string",
                        "description": null,
                        "is_bucket": false,
                        "is_pre_computed": false,
                        "bucket_info": null,
                        "_type": "Value"
                    },
                    "span_len": {
                        "dtype": "float32",
                        "description": "entity length",
                        "is_bucket": true,
                        "is_pre_computed": false,
                        "bucket_info": {
                            "_method": "bucket_attribute_specified_bucket_value",
                            "_number": 4,
                            "_setting": []
                        },
                        "_type": "Value"
                    },
                    "span_pos": {
                        "positions": [
                            0,
                            0
                        ],
                        "is_bucket": false,
                        "is_pre_computed": false,
                        "bucket_info": null,
                        "_type": "Position",
                    },
                    "span_tag": {
                        "dtype": "string",
                        "description": "entity tag",
                        "is_bucket": true,
                        "is_pre_computed": false,
                        "bucket_info": {
                            "_method": "bucket_attribute_discrete_value",
                            "_number": 4,
                            "_setting": 1
                        },
                        "_type": "Value"
                    },
                    "span_capitalness": {
                        "dtype": "string",
                        "description": "The capitalness of an entity. For example, first_caps represents only the first character of the entity is capital. full_caps denotes all characters of the entity are capital",
                        "is_bucket": true,
                        "is_pre_computed": false,
                        "bucket_info": {
                            "_method": "bucket_attribute_discrete_value",
                            "_number": 4,
                            "_setting": 1
                        },
                        "_type": "Value"
                    },
                    "span_position": {
                        "dtype": "float32",
                        "description": "The relative position of an entity in a sentence",
                        "is_bucket": true,
                        "is_pre_computed": true,
                        "bucket_info": {
                            "_method": "bucket_attribute_specified_bucket_value",
                            "_number": 4,
                            "_setting": []
                        },
                        "_type": "Value"
                    },
                    "span_chars": {
                        "dtype": "float32",
                        "description": "The number of characters of an entity",
                        "is_bucket": true,
                        "is_pre_computed": true,
                        "bucket_info": {
                            "_method": "bucket_attribute_specified_bucket_value",
                            "_number": 4,
                            "_setting": []
                        },
                        "_type": "Value"
                    },
                    "span_density": {
                        "dtype": "float32",
                        "description": "Entity density. GIven a sentence (or a sample), entity density tallies the ratio between the number of all entity tokens and tokens in this sentence",
                        "is_bucket": true,
                        "is_pre_computed": true,
                        "bucket_info": {
                            "_method": "bucket_attribute_specified_bucket_value",
                            "_number": 4,
                            "_setting": []
                        },
                        "_type": "Value"
                    },
                    "eCon": {
                        "dtype": "float32",
                        "description": "entity label consistency",
                        "is_bucket": true,
                        "is_pre_computed": true,
                        "bucket_info": {
                            "_method": "bucket_attribute_specified_bucket_value",
                            "_number": 4,
                            "_setting": []
                        },
                        "_type": "Value"
                    },
                    "eFre": {
                        "dtype": "float32",
                        "description": "entity frequency",
                        "is_bucket": true,
                        "is_pre_computed": true,
                        "bucket_info": {
                            "_method": "bucket_attribute_specified_bucket_value",
                            "_number": 4,
                            "_setting": []
                        },
                        "_type": "Value"
                    }
                },
                "is_bucket": false,
                "is_pre_computed": false,
                "bucket_info": null,
                "_type": "Set",
            },
            "length": -1,
            "is_bucket": false,
            "_type": "Sequence"
        }
    },
    "results": {
        "overall": {
            "f1_score_seqeval": {
                "metric_name": "f1_score_seqeval",
                "value": 79.02,
                "confidence_score_low": 0.0,
                "confidence_score_up": 0.0
            }
        },
        "calibration": null,
        "fine_grained": {
            "sentence_length": [
                [
                    {
                        "metric_name": "f1_score_seqeval",
                        "value": "0.8069",
                        "confidence_score_low": 0.0,
                        "confidence_score_up": 0.0,
                        "bucket_name": [
                            2.0,
                            23.0
                        ],
                        "n_samples": 275,
                        "bucket_samples": [
                            {
                                "span": "Li",
                                "text": "318",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Msigwa",
                                "text": "371",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "miezi 0",
                                "text": "5",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Dk",
                                "text": "9",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "chuo kikuu cha Burundi",
                                "text": "103",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "S Agency for Global Media",
                                "text": "466",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Li Wenliang",
                                "text": "313",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "May tarehe 0",
                                "text": "593",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Frankfurt",
                                "text": "77",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea Kaskazini",
                                "text": "540",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Rwasa",
                                "text": "96",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Poway",
                                "text": "545",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "miezi 0",
                                "text": "4",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "447",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Msigwa",
                                "text": "368",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Heil , Jr",
                                "text": "494",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Voice of America",
                                "text": "494",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Masele",
                                "text": "356",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Venessa",
                                "text": "425",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Natalia",
                                "text": "425",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bianca",
                                "text": "425",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Capri",
                                "text": "425",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Cull",
                                "text": "456",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "tarehee 00 hadi 00 June",
                                "text": "576",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hammoud",
                                "text": "136",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "CUF",
                                "text": "267",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ntaganda",
                                "text": "516",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "474",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "481",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu",
                                "text": "34",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Irungu Macharia",
                                "text": "34",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Trocadero",
                                "text": "160",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Nyalusi",
                                "text": "336",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Rwasa",
                                "text": "93",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Meghan",
                                "text": "168",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Tido",
                                "text": "221",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "0 mwezi Juni",
                                "text": "304",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Philonise",
                                "text": "389",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Calabasas",
                                "text": "416",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Texas",
                                "text": "85",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "CUF",
                                "text": "264",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "450",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Cull",
                                "text": "450",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea Kaskazini",
                                "text": "463",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Cuba",
                                "text": "463",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Brent",
                                "text": "87",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "benki ya Deutche",
                                "text": "121",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Wednesday",
                                "text": "188",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Juni 0000",
                                "text": "469",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Michael Pack",
                                "text": "469",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Gombe",
                                "text": "569",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Rwasa",
                                "text": "94",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ujerumani",
                                "text": "118",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Luftansa",
                                "text": "118",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "benki ya Japan",
                                "text": "122",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Pack",
                                "text": "471",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "471",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Cull",
                                "text": "491",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "San Diego",
                                "text": "551",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ukanda wa Gaza",
                                "text": "551",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Nyongoro",
                                "text": "114",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hariri",
                                "text": "142",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hezbollah",
                                "text": "142",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Pentagon",
                                "text": "183",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Stone",
                                "text": "254",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Fort Lauderdale",
                                "text": "254",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Maalim",
                                "text": "271",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lipumba",
                                "text": "271",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "mahakama ya uhalifu wa kimatiafa ICC",
                                "text": "275",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Masele",
                                "text": "354",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "shirika la afya duniani",
                                "text": "585",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Burundi",
                                "text": "103",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Agency for Global Media",
                                "text": "466",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Sri",
                                "text": "46",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "siku 00",
                                "text": "7",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Frankfurt",
                                "text": "77",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea",
                                "text": "540",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Poway",
                                "text": "545",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "siku saba",
                                "text": "193",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "FTSE",
                                "text": "75",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Jr",
                                "text": "494",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Voice of America - A History",
                                "text": "494",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Natalia",
                                "text": "425",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "June",
                                "text": "576",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "wiki mbili zilizopita",
                                "text": "581",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu Irungu Macharia",
                                "text": "34",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kaunti",
                                "text": "113",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "DR",
                                "text": "228",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Juni",
                                "text": "304",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Calabasas",
                                "text": "416",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Eid",
                                "text": "63",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Texas Intermediate",
                                "text": "85",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "jana",
                                "text": "357",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea",
                                "text": "463",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Cuba",
                                "text": "463",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hong",
                                "text": "531",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "siku 00",
                                "text": "285",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Juni",
                                "text": "469",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "0000 Michael Pack",
                                "text": "469",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Benki",
                                "text": "569",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ujerumani Luftansa",
                                "text": "118",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Japan",
                                "text": "122",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Dunia",
                                "text": "301",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "San",
                                "text": "551",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Gaza",
                                "text": "551",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "CAC",
                                "text": "76",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Pentagon",
                                "text": "183",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Fort Lauderdale",
                                "text": "254",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Frank Costanza",
                                "text": "260",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lipumba",
                                "text": "271",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "ICC",
                                "text": "275",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Masele",
                                "text": "354",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                [
                    {
                        "metric_name": "f1_score_seqeval",
                        "value": "0.8159",
                        "confidence_score_low": 0.0,
                        "confidence_score_up": 0.0,
                        "bucket_name": [
                            24.0,
                            32.0
                        ],
                        "n_samples": 302,
                        "bucket_samples": [
                            {
                                "span": "Ruhakana Rugunda",
                                "text": "10",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hezbollah",
                                "text": "132",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Amal",
                                "text": "132",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Nabih Berri",
                                "text": "132",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Shirika la habari la serikali ya Ethiopia",
                                "text": "170",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Jumapilli",
                                "text": "172",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "May 0",
                                "text": "295",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Masele",
                                "text": "347",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Masele",
                                "text": "347",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bethlehem",
                                "text": "394",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "S Agency for Global Media",
                                "text": "439",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "baraza la Senate",
                                "text": "439",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "464",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Gombe",
                                "text": "571",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Afrika",
                                "text": "36",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "AMISOM",
                                "text": "36",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu",
                                "text": "111",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hariri",
                                "text": "144",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "miezi mitatu",
                                "text": "158",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea kaskazini",
                                "text": "176",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea kaskazini",
                                "text": "179",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea kaskazini",
                                "text": "179",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "chama cha Democrat",
                                "text": "180",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Jugnauth",
                                "text": "286",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bunge la Tanzania",
                                "text": "359",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Msigwa",
                                "text": "373",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Chenge",
                                "text": "373",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "chama cha vijana wa Palestina",
                                "text": "395",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Calabasas",
                                "text": "411",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kushner",
                                "text": "525",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "saad Hariri",
                                "text": "145",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kobe",
                                "text": "413",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Gianna",
                                "text": "413",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lesotho",
                                "text": "591",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lesotho",
                                "text": "591",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Thomas Thabane",
                                "text": "591",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu",
                                "text": "31",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Garsen",
                                "text": "31",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "japan",
                                "text": "178",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "jumuia ya kimataifa",
                                "text": "178",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Broadway",
                                "text": "261",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bunge la Afrika",
                                "text": "349",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Harry",
                                "text": "163",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Anadolu",
                                "text": "210",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Rita",
                                "text": "274",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "CUF",
                                "text": "274",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Sy",
                                "text": "400",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Wagadougou",
                                "text": "400",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "taasisi ya Ulinzi wa Demokrasia",
                                "text": "472",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Beijing",
                                "text": "530",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Uwanja wa Tianamen",
                                "text": "530",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu",
                                "text": "30",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu",
                                "text": "109",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "lebanon",
                                "text": "139",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kabila",
                                "text": "381",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Rose Garden",
                                "text": "436",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "chuo kikuu cha Brown",
                                "text": "483",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "ntagandwa",
                                "text": "520",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Colombo",
                                "text": "42",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hariri",
                                "text": "138",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "al - Bashir",
                                "text": "281",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "jumuiya ya madola",
                                "text": "575",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kigali",
                                "text": "575",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "jumanne",
                                "text": "0",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Maalim Seif Shariff",
                                "text": "263",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Chama cha Wananchi CUF",
                                "text": "263",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lipumba",
                                "text": "270",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lipumba",
                                "text": "270",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Baraza la Wawakilishi",
                                "text": "386",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ntganda",
                                "text": "518",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "kaskazini mwa Nigeria",
                                "text": "601",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Safari",
                                "text": "129",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "siku 00",
                                "text": "129",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hezbollah",
                                "text": "132",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Amal la Nabih Berri",
                                "text": "132",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ethiopia",
                                "text": "170",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Masele",
                                "text": "347",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bethlehem",
                                "text": "394",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Agency for Global Media",
                                "text": "439",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Senate",
                                "text": "439",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Umoja wa Afrika AMISOM",
                                "text": "36",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea",
                                "text": "176",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea",
                                "text": "179",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea",
                                "text": "179",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Democrat",
                                "text": "180",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Tanzania",
                                "text": "359",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Chenge",
                                "text": "373",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Palestina",
                                "text": "395",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lisa",
                                "text": "117",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Mwanafunzi Tunashukuru",
                                "text": "145",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kobe",
                                "text": "413",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lesotho Thomas Thabane",
                                "text": "591",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "wiki mbili",
                                "text": "591",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "wiki tatu zilizopita",
                                "text": "592",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Safari",
                                "text": "31",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu - Garsen",
                                "text": "31",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Zoolander",
                                "text": "261",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Afrika",
                                "text": "349",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Eid al",
                                "text": "53",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Fitr",
                                "text": "53",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Prince Harry",
                                "text": "163",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "bahari",
                                "text": "157",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Beijing ya Uwanja",
                                "text": "530",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Eid",
                                "text": "67",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Rose Garden",
                                "text": "436",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Brown",
                                "text": "483",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Mashariki ya Kati",
                                "text": "72",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Eid",
                                "text": "72",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "al",
                                "text": "281",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bashir",
                                "text": "281",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Democrat",
                                "text": "182",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Seif Shariff",
                                "text": "263",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "CUF",
                                "text": "263",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ntganda",
                                "text": "518",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lendu",
                                "text": "518",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Nigeria",
                                "text": "601",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                [
                    {
                        "metric_name": "f1_score_seqeval",
                        "value": "0.7496",
                        "confidence_score_low": 0.0,
                        "confidence_score_up": 0.0,
                        "bucket_name": [
                            33.0,
                            44.0
                        ],
                        "n_samples": 298,
                        "bucket_samples": [
                            {
                                "span": "siku tatu",
                                "text": "55",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Rwasa",
                                "text": "92",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ndayishimiye",
                                "text": "98",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Imbonerakure",
                                "text": "107",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu",
                                "text": "115",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Garsen",
                                "text": "115",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu",
                                "text": "115",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Witu",
                                "text": "115",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "shirika la ndege la Ethiopia",
                                "text": "171",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Planespotters Civil aviation",
                                "text": "171",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea Kaskazini",
                                "text": "177",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Mhando",
                                "text": "218",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Nazi",
                                "text": "448",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ntaganda",
                                "text": "514",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "benki kuu ya dunia",
                                "text": "589",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "shirika la fedha duniani IMF",
                                "text": "589",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Tokyo",
                                "text": "79",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Sydney",
                                "text": "79",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Mhando",
                                "text": "216",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Stade de Lyon",
                                "text": "298",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lyon",
                                "text": "298",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ndugai",
                                "text": "343",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Masele",
                                "text": "343",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bunge la Afrika",
                                "text": "343",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Boston",
                                "text": "384",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bi Nixon",
                                "text": "457",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Whitworth",
                                "text": "484",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Al - Noor",
                                "text": "505",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Flightradar",
                                "text": "173",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Stiller",
                                "text": "259",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Anne Meara",
                                "text": "259",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "The Hague",
                                "text": "276",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bunge la Afrika",
                                "text": "342",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bryant",
                                "text": "419",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Naismith",
                                "text": "419",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "marekani",
                                "text": "419",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bennett",
                                "text": "479",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Philadelphia Inquirer",
                                "text": "479",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bush",
                                "text": "504",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Hariri",
                                "text": "149",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Baraza la Wawakilishi",
                                "text": "185",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "462",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "San Deigo",
                                "text": "554",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "David Nisleit",
                                "text": "554",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "San Diego",
                                "text": "554",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Jakarta",
                                "text": "174",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lion Air",
                                "text": "174",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bryant",
                                "text": "417",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Los Angeles",
                                "text": "417",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lakers",
                                "text": "417",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Nicholas Cull",
                                "text": "493",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "United States Information Agency",
                                "text": "493",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "American Public Diplomacy",
                                "text": "493",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ntaganda",
                                "text": "515",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Aceh",
                                "text": "69",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Baiturrahman",
                                "text": "69",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "The Mail on Sunday",
                                "text": "167",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "national Army",
                                "text": "249",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bunge la Tanzania",
                                "text": "377",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Victoria",
                                "text": "390",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Obama",
                                "text": "460",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "460",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Whitworth",
                                "text": "486",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Gilbrata",
                                "text": "536",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Elazig",
                                "text": "203",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Cull",
                                "text": "454",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Amnesty international",
                                "text": "324",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "kituo cha Televisheni cha New Zealand",
                                "text": "500",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Saad Hariri",
                                "text": "131",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Benki Kuu ya Tanzania",
                                "text": "197",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Wall Street",
                                "text": "83",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kobe",
                                "text": "420",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "VOA",
                                "text": "488",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lata Nott",
                                "text": "488",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Freedom Forum",
                                "text": "488",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "St Peters Basilica",
                                "text": "47",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kaaba",
                                "text": "60",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Harry",
                                "text": "162",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Octoba",
                                "text": "162",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Media rights group",
                                "text": "200",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "'The Citizen'",
                                "text": "200",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kituo cha Sheria na Haki za Binadamu",
                                "text": "201",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Bunge la Tanzania",
                                "text": "346",
                                "true_label": "ORG",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Novemba mwaka 0000",
                                "text": "441",
                                "true_label": "DATE",
                                "predicted_label": "O"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ramadhan",
                                "text": "55",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lamu - Garsen",
                                "text": "115",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Boeing",
                                "text": "171",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ethiopia",
                                "text": "171",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Planespotters Civil",
                                "text": "171",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Korea",
                                "text": "177",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Mhando",
                                "text": "218",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "IMF",
                                "text": "589",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Sydney S & P",
                                "text": "79",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "ASX",
                                "text": "79",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Jamhuri",
                                "text": "216",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Lyon in Lyon",
                                "text": "298",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Masele",
                                "text": "343",
                                "true_label": "PER",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Afrika",
                                "text": "343",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "LOC"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Boston",
                                "text": "384",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "PER"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "wiki mbili",
                                "text": "484",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "DATE"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Al",
                                "text": "505",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Noor",
                                "text": "505",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Kampuni ya Flightradar",
                                "text": "173",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Ed Sullivan",
                                "text": "259",
                                "true_label": "O",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "The Hague",
                                "text": "276",
                                "true_label": "LOC",
                                "predicted_label": "ORG"
                            },
                            {
                                "span": "Afrika",
                                "text": "342",
